

LAKHWINDER SINGH

GRAPHIC AND DESIGNER



8437746203



Lakhwindersmith203@gmail.com



125,khara,Mohali

I am a qualified and professional web and graphic designer with six month of experience in web and graphic design and website design. Hardworking and self-motivated, ready to utilize my skills and passion to further the mission of the company. Build a web sites with creativity and satisfy client with my work. Bringing a positive attitude and the willingness and motivation to learn new programs..

EXPERIENCE

GRAPHIC DESIGN

JUKUREN TECHNOLOGIES

2022 - Present

- Design multiple logos
- Design banners

WEB DESIGNER

JUKUREN TECHNOLOGIES

2022 - Present

- Creating attractive eye caching web templates
- Landing pages

SIX MONTHS INTERNSHIP IN WEB AND GRAPHIC DESIGN

OMNINOS SOLUTIONS

2022

- HTML(HTML5),CSS(CSS3),BOOTSTRAP,PHOTOSHOP,
- ILLUSTRATOR
- Landing pages

TELECALLER EXECUTIVE

DR IT · mohali, Punjab

2019 - Past

• I have worked in dr it as a telecaller executive in paytm process. I worked in there 9 to 7. That is a loan department. They provide a loan who able to take a loan. In there my work is to call a merchants and convince to a take loan.

EDUCATION

MICROCHIP TECHNOLOGY LAB

ADCA(Advance diploma of computer application)

Web designing

2018-2019

EXPERTISE

- Web Design
- Design Thinking
- HTML(HTML5)
- CSS(CSS3)
- Bootstrap
- Adobe illustrator

- Adobe photoshop
- Landing pages
- Animations

HOBBIES AND INTERESTS

 playing outdoor games, listening to music, learning new things for my ideas for my work for creative work, I keep learning from my elders and from my juniors.

COMMUNICATIVE PROFICIENCY

- Multilingual with Proficiency in:
- English
- Hindi
- Punjabi

PERSONAL INFORMATION

• Hometown:

Mukerian, hoshiarpur

- Second address:
- 125 sector,kharar,Mohali